# JACQUELINE KHAROUF

#### UX WRITER

#### CONTACT

605-430-0583

jacquelinekharouf@gmail.com

https://jacquelinekharouf.wixsite.com/mysite

24339 E. Glasgow Cir. Aurora, CO 80016

## SKILLS

Narrative, creative writing

User-centered writing

User experience research

Interpersonal interview skills

Collaboration and coordination

Organized and detailed-oriented

# EDUCATION

# UX/UI Certificate

# **University of Denver**

March 2024-September 2024

Master of Fine Arts, Creative Writing, Fiction

## **Vermont College of Fine Arts**

December 2011-January 2013

**Bachelor of Arts, Writing** 

# **Regis University**

September 2004-May 2008

Summa cum laude
Dean's List, 2004-2008
The Robert A. O'Sullivan, S.J. Memorial Award
for Excellence in Writing, 2008

#### PROFILE

Jacqueline Kharouf is a UX writer who specializes in writing user-centered content, drafting insightful research plans, and crafting user personas. With her Master of Fine Arts degree in creative writing and her writing experience, Jacqueline knows how to craft a story and to create empathetic, human personas.

Jacqueline loves to tackle overlooked (or misunderstood) user problems—such as how a single parent can better book travel accommodations; or how musicians can reach out to fans and collaborators all on one live-streaming platform; or how a local non-profit could raise awareness and keep supporters more informed.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Web Editor**

Fanfare Magazine, Tenafly, NJ

July 2023-present

- Parse html code through Fanfare software and create pushtree to upload latest reviews and issues to the Fanfare Archive, the website for Fanfare Magazine
- Create html webpages for featured articles and editorials
- Track and publish web advertisements, maintaining and communicating web sizing specifications to clients and advertisers
- Maintain email communication with clients, subscribers, the publisher, the music editor, critics, and other online inquiries
- Track subscriber data in aMember, Fanfare's preferred subscriber software

#### Reviewer

Fanfare Magazine, Tenafly, NJ

July 2016-present

- Listen to assigned classical music CDs or album downloads and write reviews of approximately 500-800 words by bi-monthly publication deadline
- Compose interview questions about album project, musical and artistic intentions, or other background information pertinent to latest album or project, and include a brief introduction
- Complete interviews with performers, composers, or collaborators for feature-length pieces, 2000 to 3000 words

# **English Writing Tutor**

Tutor.com

April 2023-July 2023

- Assist students (college, high school, or grade school age) with their written essays, English class projects, or other written assignments
- Offer students advise and guidance, especially in regard to Standard English grammar, punctuation, research formatting styles, works cited formatting, and other quidelines
- Advise students on methods to avoid plagiarism and encourage students to develop their own written style

# JACQUELINE KHAROUF

## UX WRITER

CONTACT
605-430-0583
jacquelinekharouf@gmail.com
https://jacquelinekharouf.wixsite.com/mysite
24339 E. Glasgow Cir., Aurora, CO 80016
DESIGN THINKING
<ul> <li>Jacqueline applies her storytelling, organizational, sketching, and Figma skills to solve user experience problems.</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>First, she understands a conflict by empathizing with a persona's motivations and goals, as well as pain points and obstacles.</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Then she crafts a plan, schedules interviews, creates a survey, and asks questions.</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Finally, she visualizes a solution for the user, experimenting with structures and shapes that enhance the user's journey.</li> </ul>
Joel Flegler, Publisher, Fanfare
201-567-3908
fanfaremag@aol.com
James A. Altena, Music Editor, Fanfare
215-676-9412
fanfaremagazinereviews@gmail.com

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Records Coordinator I**

Noble Energy Inc., Denver Records Center, Denver, CO

Jan. 2013-Mar. 2017

- Direct contractors to accomplish daily tasks in an accurate and orderly manner
- · Process documentation for filing
- Attend weekly meetings with lead records coordinator and other records coordinators

## **Contract Data Technician**

Noble Energy Inc., Denver Records Center, Denver, CO

Nov. 2011-Dec. 2012

- Process land well and division order documents for filing
- Organize, move, and transfer files for sales, special projects, and record maintenance
- Data entry, such as entering new file set-ups into data information system, barcoding, and auditing files

# **Computer Literacy Instructor**

Emily Griffith Technical College, Language Learning Center, Sept. 2010-Nov. 2011 Denver, CO

- Instruct students on basic computer usage, including typing and formatting techniques
- Plan lessons based on Colorado Refugee English as a Second Language computer curriculum

## **Administrative Assistant**

Emily Griffith Technical College, Language Learning Center, Jan. 2009-Nov. 2011 Denver, CO

- Test and place refugee students in Colorado Refugee English as a Second Language program
- Register new and returning adult students in English as a Second Language classes
- Administer Best Plus English assessment test
- · Compile and edit monthly department newsletter

## **Classroom Tutor**

Emily Griffith Technical College, Language Learning Center, Aug. 2008-Jan. 2009 Denver. CO

- Tutor low-level English students, providing instruction and facilitating group conversation
- Assist English instructors by taking attendance and compiling instructional materials